[Music] let's
[Música]
see something else that's also about
a ver otra cosa que también trata sobre
Ricky let's see something else that's
Ricky vamos a ver otra cosita que
also about Ricky okay And it's that
también trata sobre Ricky vale Y es que
well it's already been made public that Lali has
bueno ya se ha hecho público que Lali ha
filed a complaint in the
puesto una denuncia en el juzgado de la
women's court okay This one for gender violence
mujer vale Este de violencia de género
has filed a complaint against Ricky Eddie
le ha puesto una denuncia a Ricky Eddie
for several reasons Okay among which is
por varios motivos Okay entre los que se
what Ricky did that this
encuentra lo que hizo Ricky que esto
well We can say this because he
bueno Esto lo podemos decir porque él
himself admitted it Ricky took
mismo lo reconoció Ricky le cogió el
Lali's phone while Lali was sleeping
teléfono a Lali mientras que Lali dormía
to record conversations due to
para registrarle conversaciones por
insecurity Okay and a series of
inseguridad Vale y una serie de
other issues that we're going to listen to here
cuestiones más que vamos a escuchar aquí
to see if they say them okay but they're
a ver si las dicen vale pero son
insults towards her and things like that
insultos hacia ella y cosas por el
okay because I thought that this
estilo vale porque yo pensaba que esto
was something that was being planned to
era algo que se estaba planificando para
start pulling strings I'm not a lawyer I'm not a
empezar a mover hilos no soy abogado no
judge but no no this the complaint was already
soy juez pero no no esto ya la denuncia
filed a long time ago months ago I think in
se puso hace tiempo hace meses creo de
fact and and not only was it filed a long
hecho y y no solamente se puso hace
time ago but there are already phases I mean it's already going well it's
tiempo sino que que ya hay fases O sea
advanced let's go grandpa and
ya va ya va adelantado vamos abuelo y
Pablo goes up to testify with Ricky cinema
Pablo sube a declarar a Ricky cine
cigarette man of course I think
cigarrillo hombre claro yo creo que
Ricky will defend himself [ __ ] Ricky
Ricky se defenderá de [__] madre Ricky
will defend himself from  [ __ ] great, sure, eh,
se defenderá de putísima madre seguro eh
you want to browse the
quieres Navegar de forma segura en
internet safely and also access all the
internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix, HBO Max, or Disney Plus,
como Netflix hbo Max o Disney Plus
cyberghost VPN And I don't know if you
cyberghost VPN Y es que no sé si lo
know, but there is content that is not available in your country
sabes pero hay contenidos que en tu país
and with this
no están disponibles y con este
little trick you can access all the
truquillo puedes acceder a todo el
content wherever you are, I don't know if you
contenido estés donde estés no sé si
know what a VPN is, but it's an
sabes lo que es una VPN pero es una
extension that you put on your internet
extensión que le pones a tu internet con
that masks your IP and apart from
la que enmascara la IP y aparte de
browsing completely safely and anonymously
Navegar completamente seguro y anónimo
without anyone being able to know who you are and
sin que nadie pueda saber quién eres y
where you are, it helps you access
dónde estás Te sirve para acceder
some content that is blocked
algunos contenidos que están bloqueados
in your country, there are movies and series on your
en tu país hay películas y series en tus
favorite platforms that are not
plataformas favoritas que no están
available, there are television programs,
disponibles hay programas de televisión
for example on Mediaset, content that
por ejemplo en mediaset contenidos que
if you try to watch them outside of Spain
si los intentas ver fuera de España
has a geoblock that doesn't
tienen un geobloqueo que no te lo
allow it. Well, with cyberghost VPN, that's
permite Pues con cyberghost VPN eso se
over. Apart from being protected by
acabó Aparte de estar protegido
browsing anonymously, you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet, you will also have total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data, ultra-fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad Ultra rápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live broadcasts without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you  Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever you
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
want. Also, take advantage of a full 83%
quieras además Aprovecha todo un 83 de
discount using the link I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
left in the description of this video. And be careful
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try Cyber ​​Ghost VPN for
ojo porque puedes probar Cyber Ghost VPN
45 days without obligation. If you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced, ask for a refund and they will
convence pides el reembolso y te
return the item. So don't wait any longer
devuelven la pza Así que no esperes más
to protect your connection and improve your
para proteger tu conexión y aumentar tu
internet experience. Go ahead and click
experiencia en internet correale click
on the link in the description and take advantage of
al enlace de la descripción y aprovecha
this super cyberghost VPN offer to
esta super oferta cyberghost VPN para
browse completely free and secure.
navegar completamente libre y seguro
We continue with the eh. It seems that things are
seguimos con el eh Parece que la cosa va
serious. It seems that they have already happened. I
en serio Parece que ya han pasado es que
don't know what procedures or what events they do
no sé qué trámites o qué sucesos hacen
before there are phases of the trial or the
antes de hay fases el juicio o de los
trials that they will have on this issue.
juicios que tendrán sobre este tema
Because if he comments that it goes beyond
Porque si comenta que va más allá de lo
checking the mobile, be careful,
de revisar el móvil cuidado cuidado ya
because eh, man, let's see, there are more things, there are
que eh hombre a ver hay más cosas hay
more things. Thanks to the subscriber who
más cosas Gracias al suscriptor que me
passed this on to me, we have what I'm going to
ha pasado esto tenemos lo que os voy a
show you next since the other
enseñar a continuación ya que el otro
day, I think this is not from today, it's from a
día creo que esto no es de hoy es de
few days ago. Pablo
hace unos días Pablo en su directo
commented the following in his live broadcast, but let's put sound on it,
comentó lo siguiente per ponle sonido
friend. Oh, wait, I can't hear it, give me  wait
amigo Ah esperad que no lo se oye dadme
a minute is it true the trial will be
un momento es verdad el juicio será
public in the future I want to see it I don't
público en un futuro quiero verlo No
think so Tomeu I don't think so I don't know we will see him
creo tomeu no creo no sé lo veremos
testifying maybe something I don't know the
declarando a lo mejor algo No lo sé la
truth there are times when it is leaked but I don't
verdad hay veces que se filtra pero no
know okay I think that's it Now you
lo sé vale creo que es esto Ahora sí se
have to listen I didn't understand anything what
tiene que escuchar No he entendido nada
Ricky wants the audio the audio
lo que quier de Ricky el audio el audio
was a metaphor it was a metaphor a
era una metáfora era una metáfora una
metaphor this I have the
metáfora esto tengo permiso de la
client's permission to say it there is a lawsuit Yes
clienta para decirlo hay una demanda Sí
yes send bits that If you want me to
sí que mande bits eso Si quieres que te
answer keep sending bits there is
conteste sigue mandando bit hay una
a lawsuit for the right to there is a lawsuit for
demanda por derecho a hay una demanda en
protection of
protección a la
gender violence there is a Sorry
por violencia de género hay una Perdón
[ __ ] I'm used to
[__] ya estoy acostumbrado a las
lawsuits for protection of the right to honor
demandas en protección al derecho honor
there is a complaint for gender violence
hay una denuncia por violencia de género
gender violence because checking
violencia de género porque lo de revisar
the cell phone falls under that plan
el móvil entra dentro de eso plan
checking the cell phone falls under a
revisar el móvil entra dentro de una
complaint of gender violence because of
denuncia de violencia de género porque
course I don't know what other things will come in that
claro no sé qué cosas más entrarán que
Lali will have said that Rick supposedly did to her this
habrá contado Lali que supuestamente le
is the issue against him
habrá hecho Rick es el tema contra él
for various reasons in Zaragoza in the
por varias razones en Zaragoza en el
court of violence against women
juzgado de violencia contra la mujer
number two in Zaragoza he will be summoned
número dos de Zaragoza se le citará
who feeds ait low bar Kelvin
quién da de comer ait barra baja Kelvin
donated
donado
little words Ah  No, I'm not messing with him either.
palabritas Ah No tampoco me meto con é
But also, it's that Zaragoza,
Pero además además es que Zaragoza por
why is that? I have no idea, the l was from
qué eso no tengo ni p idea la l era de
Zaragoza or all this in Zaragoza, that
Zaragoza o todo esto en Zaragoza eso
Ricky, I don't care that Ricky is not here yet, on the
Ricky me da igual que Ricky todavía no
contrary, he still hasn't
está de contrario todavía no se ha
appeared. Well, anyway. Thank you Kevin, he hasn't
personado bueno en fin Gracias Kevin no
appeared. He's making it up, I mean,
se ha personado est inventando digo yo
terrible. Ricky can win whatever he wants,
terrible podrá ganar todo lo que quiera
but
Ricky pero los titulares son los que
people are looking for headlines. I don't know. I don't know what's
busca la gente es que no lo sé No lo sé
behind all this, but I repeat, it's that
habrá detrás de todo esto pero repito es
we are not aware that she is
que que no somos conscientes de que es
a girl who said that in front of how many millions
una chica que delante de cuánto millones
of people. So I
de personas dijo eso Entonces yo me
expect anything, he will say in a video,
espero cualquier cosa él en un vídeo
in a viral video in front of
dirá en en un vídeo viral delante de
millions of people, he admitted about the
millones de personas admitió lo del
phone, but then he starts with the insults. I just
teléfono pero luego parte los insultos
showed you an example. Okay,
os acabo de enseñar un ejemplo Vale
now, now we'll see a few more. Take off your
ahora ahora veremos unos cuantos más os
pants because when this comes out,
los pantalones porque cuando salga esto
when they tell what is being
cuando cuenten por lo que se está
reported. I imagine
denunciando Yo me imagino cosas
surreal things, I imagine something implausible,
surrealistas me imagino algo inverosímil
I already have, I am prepared, I am
yo ya tengo yo estoy preparado yo estoy
prepared for the day that we react to
preparado para el día que reaccionemos a
this because it will surely be public and they
esto porque seguramente se público y lo
will tell it. I am prepared  to
contarán yo estoy preparado para
listen to some really crazy ideas from Hoya who
escuchar auténticas locuras idas de Hoya
knows what's coming next
a saber a saber lo que se viene
we hope Well there's one thing I didn't
esperamos Bueno yo hay una cosa que no
know was public man they put it
sabía que era pública tío me lo pusieron
in the comments box today he says never
en la caja de comentarios hoy dice nunca
forget that Ricky admitted
hay que olvidar que el Ricky reconoció
in the debate with Dallas that he locked himself
en el debate con Dallas que se encerró
in the bathroom to hit himself when he
en el baño a pegarse a sí mismo cuando
found out about the cuckolding someone with a
se enteró de los cuernos alguien con una
head like that must have done another
cabeza Así ha tenido que hacer otra
well This is what people have put to me in
bueno Esto me lo ha puesto la gente en
the comments on the last videos So
los comentarios de los vídeos últimos O
he said that in public he
sea que eso lo dijo él en público lo
acknowledged it in public too about the
reconoció é en público también lo del
bathroom thing I mean that type of behavior and
baño o sea ese tipo de comportamientos y
actions there are things that what I have to
de acciones hay cosas que que lo que
say about him is that this man
tengo que decir de él es que este señor
has insulted he has humiliated he has had
ha insultado ha vejado ha ha tenido
violent attitudes I imagine Ricky
actitudes violentas me imagino al Ricky
with some popcorn be careful with some
con unas palomitas cuidado con unas
popcorn what he eats let him eat popcorn
palomitas que coma que coma palomitas
that the guy has also played before I
que le chul ha jugado también antes he
put okay before I put an example
puesto vale antes he puesto un ejemplo
which was Ricky in the podcast in the
que era el de el Ricky en el podc en el
delo podcast talking like that about Ali okay let's
podcast de delo hablando así de Ali vale
see tell me what you think Hey maybe it
a ver decirme ustedes qué os parece Oye
's nonsense maybe  it's
que a lo mejor es una tontería que a lo
nonsense they abused me
mejor es una tontería abusaron de mí
at most he tells me what I could have
como mucho me dice lo que pude llegar a
done maybe was suck his [ __ ] I
hacer a lo mejor fue chuparle la [__]
don't know what I mean I say [ __ ] kick stand
no s qué tal digo digo [__] pate
up another chapter I say at most I
párate otro capítulo digo como mucho
say but you remember I don't say I don't
digo pero te acuerdas no di no me
remember anything I say at most because it's that I
acuerdo de nada digo como mucho porque
don't notice anything It's that I think that
es que no noto nada Es que yo creo que
nothing happened be careful because we are in
no pasó nada cuidado porque estamos en
Spain there are more things out there on
España hay hay más cosillas por ahí en
Twitter he also insulted her on a couple of
Twitter también la insultó en un par de
occasions there is one there are a few girls
ocasiones hay una hay unas cuantas tía
he beyond what Ali can say if it
él más allá de lo que Ali pueda decir si
's true or a lie we don't
es verdad o mentira nosotros eso no lo
know but seeing the situation Well of course
sabemos pero viendo el percal Pues claro
you can imagine but of course We don't
te lo puedes imaginar pero claro No lo
know it's one's word against
sabemos es la palabra de una contra el
another per having No it's not the word
de otro per teniendo No no es la palabra
they are [ __ ] things that have been seen in
son [__] cosas que se han visto en
public many times tell us that we are
público muchas veces cuenta que estamos
in Spain he admitted to a crime it is that it is like that it
en España él admitió un delito es que es
seems surreal but it is that it is like that
así parece surrealista pero es que es
he admitted to a crime in a
así él admitió un delito en un vídeo
public video that he had reviewed the mo
Público de que le había revisado el mó
is that he admitted it that's the issue tentations with
es que lo admitió es el tema tentas con
my client and and that's it and that's it Okay
mi mandante y y ya está y ya está Vale
but he says he has proof eh And if it
pero él dice que tiene pruebas eh Y si
is from  Zaragoza So he's his ex
es de Zaragoza Entonces es su ex
indeed yes yes Ali no but this already
efectivamente sí sí Ali no pero esto ya
Ah of course Ali is from Zaragoza so that's why he
Ah claro que Ali es de Zaragoza entonces
's hao Hello my old man very
por eso lo est hao Hola mi viejo bien
tasty What's up Dark Thank you very much we
sabroso Qué pasa Dark Muchísimas gracias
know but this he already said
lo sabemos pero esto ya lo dijo
listen to me It's that the the the Scoop was
escúchame Es que la la la Primicia la
given by a friend of Ali on her channel you know
dio una amiga del Ali en su canal sabes
who broke the news although I'll also
quién dio la noticia aunque también te
tell you cell How long do you have to
digo cel Cuánto tiempo tienes que
reside in Andorra to get the
residir en andorra para que te la
nationality But that doesn't matter at all
nacionalidad Pero eso no importa nada
here okay it was a doubt I say it because
aquí vale era una duda lo digo porque
by the way I took a photo with the two of them
por cierto me hice una foto con las dos
at the door of the court in Zaragoza it's
en la puerta del juzgado en Zaragoza
really cool it's the photo we just saw
chulísima es la foto que acabamos de ver
and I am the lawyer Yes Ali's lawyer
y yo soy el abogado Sí el abogado de Ali
Yes and the video and the Scoop was given with
Sí y el vídeo y la Primicia se dio con
the permission of the one who by the way is a
el permiso de la que por cierto es un
lovely girl another of the I wouldn't like I would
amor de chica otra de las no me gustaría
n't like to have the pleasure but I don't
no me gustaría tener el gusto pero no
have I don't have I'm sorry Thank you Gen
tengo no tengo lo siento Gracias Gen
baraj Kelvin has donated 100 vitaz gr here
baraj Kelvin ha donado 100 vitaz gr aquí
comes nauter's participation And
viene la participación de nauter Y
how much would I earn from ler's lawsuit
cuánto ganaría por la demanda de ler
Ricky or nauter thanks And how much would I earn
Ricky o nauter gracias Y cuánto ganaría
from laser's lawsuit  Ricky or nauter
por la demanda de laser Ricky o nauter
eh I'll tell you Ricky's It's that I think
eh Te digo la de Ricky Es que yo creo
that all three of them are going to be sentenced to
que las tres les van a condenar en
costs Nauter's how much am I going to get
costas la de nauter cuánto voy a ganar
for it wait 65 + 330 1995 for 1.21 let's
por ella espérate 65 + 330 1995 por 1.21
see in theory Nauter in theory Nauter
a ver en teoría nauter en teoría nauter
is that of course I'm jotting down
es que claro estoy haciendo memoria
because too many
porque es que han pasado demasiadas
things have happened in these last few days for weeks
cosas en estos últimos días para semanas
in theory he is reported because in
en teoría está denunciado poras en
theory we are mixing issues but in
teoría estamos mezclando temas pero en
theory he is pun 21 243 he has to
teoría está pun 21 243 lo tiene que
pay it are the costs prosecutor okay
pagar son las costas procurador vale
but elrick being a criminal case it
pero elrick al ser un penal ya depende
also depends on the sentence imposed on him it
también de la pena que le impongan
depends on many things criminal trial criminal of
depende de muchas cosas juicio penal
course it is gender violence
penal claro es una violencia de género
supposedly Nauter's will be
supuestamente el de nauter será
different no because that's where we're talking about
diferente no porque ahí estamos hablando
Nauter's case it is for men let's see it
Ya de lo de nauter es par hombre a ver
is gender violence But be careful, careful I
es violencia de género Pero cuidado
repeat, careful, damn it I repeat he
cuidado repito cuidado [__] repito
admitted to a crime According to Spanish law
admitió un delito Según la ley española
looking at his cell phone be extensible
mirar el móvil ser extensible viejo
tasty old man I don't know if he should do it man
sabroso Es que no sé si hacerlo tío
you think we would get something in
ustedes creen que conseguiríamos algo en
the extensible is that if I knew that
el extensible es que si yo supiera que
yes but can you imagine that I put myself at
sí pero te imaginas que me pongo a las
12 in the morning on Sunday and we didn't even make it
12 de la mañana el domingo y no llegamos
to 3 in the afternoon because people are
ni a las 3 de la tarde porque la gente
n't giving anything so I don't know if we should do it
no da nada entonces no no sé si hacerlo
or we keep getting it day by day let's
o seguimos consiguiéndolo día a día a
see it's not going bad eh I mean the box is going well
ver no va mal eh o sea va bien la caja
eh but I think that whoever
eh pero yo creo que ya quien haya
wanted to donate this month has already donated and I
querido donar este mes ya ha donado y yo
think that by next month or the
creo que ya hasta el mes que viene o
end of the month I don't think people will donate
finales de mes no creo que la gente done
much more but I'm not in a hurry
mucho más pero tampoco tengo mucha prisa
either eh I mean this already I think that with
eh o sea esto ya yo creo que ya con
these 3000 and something I already have the
estos 3000 y pico Ya tengo la
answer to the demand and the rest
contestación a la demanda y ya el resto
of the phases next month
de fases el mes que viene viene otra
something else comes next month something else You know like that you
cosa el mes que viene otra Sabes así
know like little by little it's not
sabes o sea poco a poco tampoco hace
necessary let's say I would do it eh an
falta vamos que yo lo haría eh un
extendable I mean I don't know if we could
extensible o sea no sé si podríamos
do an extendable of how much every every
hacer un un extensible de Cuánto cada
how much like every 50 10 minutes more
cada cuánto o sea cada 50 10 minutos más
for example it wouldn't be no for example I'm
por ejemplo no serían no por ejemplo me
making it up every 50 euros 10
lo estoy inventando cada 50 eur 10
minutes plus 300 euros an hour would come out and
minutos más 300 eur la hora saldría e y
we said man I would put a
hemos dicho que hombre yo le pondría un
limit on it  about 15 hours or so man yeah
tope de de unas 15 horas o así tío sí a
maybe we would get another 3000 or
lo mejor conseguiríamos otros 3000 o
something like that if we get another 3000
algo así si conseguimos otros 3000
we are there until 3 or 4 in the morning of course
estamos hasta las 3 4 de la mañana claro
your partner is a crime and he admitted it in
tu pareja es delito y él lo admitió en
a video but I don't think
un vídeo pero no creo yo que que
we would get to the case of it is different it is
llegásemos el caso de es diferente es
obvious it is not the same but it is cost okay but
obio no es lo mismo per es costia vale
yes the costs are that's what I
pero sí las costas son eso lo que te he
told you 1 well that's it but in Andorra and
dicho 1 bueno eso ya pero en andorra y
the same laws on gender violence I
las mismas leyes de violencia de género
have no idea we can ask
no tengo ni idea Le podremos preguntar a
chat gpt we asked chat gpt with
chat gpt le preguntamos a chat gpt con
Legal frameworks to address
Marcos legales para abordar violencia de
gender violence the specific laws vary between
género las ley específicas varían entre
Andorra and Spain I'm going to put put it
andorra y España voy a poner ponerle
quiet like in Andorra although the
calla como en andorra aunque las
regulations being legally sanctioned in
normativas ser sancionada legalmente en
Spain is what I was going to tell you I don't
España es lo que os iba a decir que no
know exactly how Andorra will go but due to
sé exactamente có ira andorra pero por
the proximity it is probably something
la cercanía seguramente sea algo
similar to what it is in Spain and in itself
parecido a lo que sea en España y en sí
Pablo has put it because he knows what
Pablo le ha puesto porque sabe lo que
France does So I don't know I don't know
hace Francia Así que no lo sé No lo sé
how it will vary but then there has also been
cómo variará per luego también ha habido
this conflict no that utbh has attacked
este conflicto no que utbh ha atacado a
Pablo no  I know, I'm obviously
Pablo no sé yo yo entre discusiones de
not going to get involved in the discussions between the two of them,
ellos dos no me voy a meter
but anyway, I'm going to read it to
evidentemente pero bueno lo voy a leer a
see. It seemed very gratuitous to me because I
ver a mí me parecio muy gratuito porque
apologize to the
es que pido perdón a la comunidad de
internet community and the world in general for having
internet y al mundo en general por haber
helped this man believe himself
ayudado a este hombre a creerse
relevant. I don't understand at this
relevante Es que no entiendo en en este
moment, at this point, I mean, I can
momento en este punto o sea yo puedo
criticize Pablo for some things, not from
criticar a Pablo por algunas cosas no de
weeks ago, the fights he's had
semanas atrás las peleas que ha tenido
with these people, but this, believing himself
con esta gente pero esto creerse
relevant, let's see, have they hired him as a
relevante a ver lo han contratado como
lawyer, I mean, Lali, uh, looked for lawyers and I
abogado o sea Lali eh buscó abogados y y
imagine he would look for. Well, there are people who are
me imagino que buscaría Pues gente que
already in the environment of his
haya ya que esté en el entorno de su
channel, not that I know of who has won cases
canal no que sepa que haya ganado casos
and such. Pablo may fall better or worse
y tal no Pablo podrá caer mejor o peor
on YouTube and he causes trouble or he doesn't cause trouble, whatever
en YouTube y la lía o no la lía todo lo
you want, okay, Gibel supports you. By
que queráis vale gibel te apoya Por
the way, what has Anderson said about
cierto En qué Anderson en qué ha dicho
Guel lately? Dark, I think it
algo guel últimamente Dark creo que
would be great if it's the same for a minute, a
sería genial si es un igual un minuto un
minute, but a two minute, a two minute,
d un minuto pero un dó un minuto un d un
I can spend a whole day, why would
minuto puedo echar día entero para qué
a two minute be 60? I mean, if we spend
un d un minuto sería 60 O sea si echamos
12 hours we would earn 700  utbh is going to
12 horas ganaríamos 700 utbh va a
defend Ricky Yes that's why I'm telling you that
defender a Ricky Sí por eso te digo que
I'm not going to get involved in what I see if
yo no voy a meterme en lo que he yo si
he defends Ricky because he's his friend You
él defiende a Ricky porque es su amigo
know I wouldn't get involved in this issue and I wouldn't
Sabes Yo no me metería en este tema y no
say anything let's see More knowing that Ricky
diría nada a ver Más sabiendo que Ricky
has recognized It's that you know So what's
ha reconocido Es que sabes O sea qué
Pablo's fault that they
culpa tiene Pablo de que lo hayan
hired him in this sense But of course
contratado en este sentido Pero claro
Here he is attacking Pablo This guy one
Aquí está atacando a Pablo Este pavo un
day does a live with Giovanni Carril
día te hace un directo con giovan carril
and the next day he takes a picture with
y al día siguiente se hace una foto con
his historical cube that he reported a
su cubo histórico que denunció una
sexual assault to cover up some horns
agresión sexual para tapar unos cuernos
and agreeing to legally represent her
y prestándose a representarla legalmente
in a false complaint against Biogen It's that
en una denuncia falsa de biogen Es que
this no I would not have started to say
esto no yo no me hubiera puesto a decir
this with that background of the trial you could
esto con ese fondo del juicio podrías
finally say if I am a judge answering
decir por fin si soy juez contestando a
Javi's song you are a judge a kiss a
la canción de Javi eres juez un beso un
kiss a false complaint is that it is not a
beso una denuncia falsa es que no es una
false complaint eh another thing is that Ricky
denuncia falsa eh otra cosa es que Ricky
is acquitted or you do not understand me but
salga absuelto o no me entiendes pero
a false complaint is that you invent
una denuncia falsa es que tú te invente
the
los los
acts the complaint I from what I
actos la denuncia yo por lo que tengo
understand I do not know to what extent Andy has commented
entendido no sé hasta dónde ha comentado
Andy is that have a tweet open here
Andy es que ten aquí abierto un tweet
because now also  let's talk about it about
porque ahora también vamos a comentarlo
delo that delo there's also a
de delo que delo también hay una
new story but my computer has restarted
historia nueva pero se me ha reiniciar
wait I'm going to see the
el ordenador espérate voy a ver el
history for a moment that this live I
historial un momento eso esto el directo
prepared it myself like [ __ ] I do
me lo he preparado yo como a las [__]
n't remember what the Twitter
Es que no me acuerdo cómo era el Twitter
of this girl was like Javi you're going to
de la de la chiquilla esta Javi vas a
charge by the hour it only took 3 minutes
cobrar por hora solo ocupo 3 minutos
face sweating a kiss Tun Tum there's no more
cara sudando un beso Tun Tum ya ya no
fabric today luare still eh today I don't
falta tela hoy luare todavía eh hoy no
think I'll stop recording a video the
creo que me pare grabar vídeo el
main one because I don't have time
principal porque es que no me va tiempo
[ __ ] it's that I can't find the
[__] es que no encuentro el twit de la
girl's tweet Andy reveals [ __ ] where I
chiquilla Andy revela [__] dónde lo
have it I curse everything it's that I can't
tengo me cago en todo es que no lo
find it but I need it to comment on let's
encuentro pero lo necesito para comentar
see if you can look for it for me Lu
lo de a ver si me lo puedes buscar Lu
please in the meantime to comment on
porfa de mientras para comentarlo de
delox Andy's Twitter that she doesn't care about
delox El Twitter de Andy que la da igual
anyway I mean it's not a
de todas maneras O sea no es una
false accusation this means that
denuncia falsa esto quiere decir que
Ricky is guilty no no this we'll have to
Ricky sea culpable no no esto habrá que
wait and see what
esperar a ver que es lo que dice la
justice says now a false accusation
justicia ahora bien una denuncia falsa
How how how are you going to start saying
Cómo cómo cómo vas a ponerte a decir
this to carate dem mandel Ali you also
esto para carate dem mandel Ali también
know in a false accusation of violence
sabes en una denuncia falsa de viogen
against Ricky  Eddie, I mean without you being
contra Ricky Eddie o sea sin tú estar
present if you if you form if it's that not
presente si tú si tú form si es que ni
even I dare ever tell
siquiera yo me atrevo nunca a decir a
someone who has filed a false complaint
alguien que ha puesto una denuncia falsa
about things that I think so or I mean one thing
en cosas que yo lo opine o sea una cosa
is a false complaint which is that I
es una denuncia falsa que es que yo te
catch you and report you for something that
coja y te denuncie por algo que en
really didn't happen in mind another
realidad no ha pasado en en mente otra
thing is that I file a complaint against you
cosa es que yo te ponga una denuncia
but then justice doesn't rule in my favor
pero luego la justicia no me de la razón
luar is a tit that Andy posted today in
luar es un tet que ha puesto Andy hoy en
which she explains exclusively
el que ella Explica en exclusiva
news about the Delos trial that
novedades sobre el juicio de delos que
was Delos accused in a topic Put
estaba delos imputados en un tema Pon
Delos and trial or something like that or scam or I don't
delos y juicio o algo así o estafa o no
know and it will come out eh I already have it I already
sé y te saldrá eh Ya lo tengo ya lo
have it thank you very much this has been it has
tengo muchas gracias está ha sido ha
been Lili faster but what am I
sido Lili más rápida pero qué es lo que
telling you So it is not a
te digo O sea que no es una denuncia
false complaint because it could be that Lali considers
falsa pues puede ser que Lali considere
that she has been mistreated we will see the
que ha sido maltratada ya se verá las
things that she has filed the complaint is not
cosas que ha puesto la denuncia no es
a false complaint she filed the thing about the
una denuncia falsa la le ha puesto lo de
phone she filed some insults and she
lo del teléfono ha puesto unos insultos
also filed a series of humiliations and she presented a series of
también y ha presentado una serie de
things that also happened in private
cosas que también pasaron en privado
okay or so that's it  They tell us we
vale o sea eso ya si lo cuentan ellos lo
will discuss it here okay the question
comentaremos aquí vale la la cuestión
that Sergio got angry okay he is here
que se ha enfadado Sergio vale está aquí
fighting with people he is controlled
peleándose con la gente está controlado
by Jo and he uses it for his
por Jo y lo usa para sus platos
personal dishes Not me until me
personales Yo no yo hasta que yo ya
when I found out about this if I'm not
cuando me enteré de esto si no me
mistaken when I found out about this
equivoco yo ya cuando me enteré de esto
the complaint had already been filed I didn't know
ya estaba puesta la denuncia yo no sabía
that he had contacted me I can I
que al había contactado con yo puedo yo
can probably count on the fingers of one hand
puedo contar con los dedos de una mano
the times that I spoke with
seguramente las veces que hablado yo con
Lalin I asked him about the Tudor issue
lalin le pregunté por el tema de tudor
if he would give me the final sentence that I
si me pasaba la sentencia en firme que
remember he was there I wasn't I
me acuerdo que ahí estaba yo no estaba
was in Madrid I think and he answered me
Estaba en Madrid yo creo y me contestó
very badly he didn't want to give it to me then there are a
muy mal no me lo quiso dar luego hay un
couple of times maybe we have
par de veces a lo mejor que hemos
talked about some content that I have
hablado de algún contenido que yo he
made but I don't do this what I have
hecho pero yo esto no lo que no tengo
nothing to do with this what do you want me to
nada que ver con esto que quieres que te
tell you Victoria a kiss They will never be able to
diga Victoria un beso Nunca van a poder
prove otherwise okay the idea
demostrar lo contrario vale la idea no
is not to win the case but to use it this is a
es ganar el caso sino usarlo este es
follower of these
seguidor de de las cuentas estas del
lerl accounts and those people okay Okay but a
lerl Y esa gente vale Okay pero un
little bit of integrity it can't be that you
poquito de integridad no puede ser que
go dev based critical of
vayas dev basado crítico con el
feminism and the instrumentalization
feminismo y con la instrumentalización
of the laws of the Team  purple armpit and the
de las leyes del Team sobaco morado y al
next day you show off with someone
día siguiente te farandu con alguien
like Lali to rape
como Lali para meterle una viogen a
Ricky Eddy Let's see, Ricky Eddie has
Ricky Eddy A ver es que Ricky Eddie ha
publicly admitted that he has admitted to
reconocido en público que ha reconocido
a crime So no, I wouldn't have
un delito O sea que no yo no me hubiera
gotten into this and he says lerl Well, what a mess he's
metido en esto y dice lerl Pues menuda
made me, what a mess you've made me, son of a [ __ ]
me ha liado menuda me has liado hijo
with this guy and he says seriously, they
[__] con el pavo este y le dice serio a
would have continued to report you and without
ti te habrían seguido denunciando y sin
Pablo FR yes, yes, if it hadn't
Pablo FR es que sí es que si no hubiera
been with one lawyer it would have been with
sido con un abogado hubiera sido con
another but Lali's case is the same as Lali's
otro pero lo de Lali es igual a Lali
too, I mean, Lali would have, let's see,
también o sea Lali hubiera vamos a ver
Lali was going to report Ricky at
que Lali iba a denunciar a Ricky en
some point, that's not it, that hadn't been
algún momento eso no Vamos eso no
listed since 2000 or so, I mean, the
cotizaba desde el año 2000 y pico o sea
thing about Lali
lo de que Lali
and all the kids and pambisitos at the
e toda la chavalería y pambisitos a la
same time answering this and all the
vez respondiendo esto y todas las
accounts that I see silenced or
cuentas que te veo silenciadas o
blocked, most of what I remember
bloqueadas en su mayoría qué recuerdo
says well, well, These are tweets that
dice que bueno pues Estos son twit que
we'll comment on when whatever happens happens, I
comentaremos cuando pase lo que sea
can understand that you don't like
puedo entender que no te caiga bien
Pablo look here Pablo has
Pablo mira aquí Pablo se ha des
untagged himself It's that Pablo doesn't mention
etiquetado es Es que Pablo no menciona
Sergio but this is  the
Sergio pero este es el argumento más
stupidest argument I've ever heard is that
estúpido que he escuchado resulta que
Pablo commits the Terrible sin of
Pablo comete el Terrible pecado de
working but the thing is that anyway
trabajar pero es que de todas manera
even if it hadn't been Pablo you're
aunque no hubiera sido Pablo eres
extremely stupid apart from being ignorant if you
tontísima aparte de ignorante si tú
have a channel in which you do
tienes un canal en el que haces
activism against drugs you represent
activismo contra las drogas representas
a member of a but let's see
a miembro de un pero es que vamos a ver
that Pablo is against eh the
que Pablo esté en contra de eh que se
abuse of gender violence laws does
abuse de las leyes de violencia de
not imply that he can't
género no implica que no pueda
hire someone to denounce
contratarlo a alguien para denunciar a a
a person who he believes has
una persona que considera que ha
committed crimes man what would
cometido delitos hombre lo que me
seem hypocritical to me would be for Pablo to
parecería una hipocresía sería que Pablo
admit a case in which it is a
admi tie un caso en el que sea una
false accusation How do you untag yourself on
denuncia falsa Cómo se des etiqueta uno
Twitter you can untag yourself and leave
Twitter te puedes desetiquetar y sales
the thread the thing is that Pablo doesn't mention utbh
del hilo es que Pablo no menciona a utbh
at all nor is he going to answer But what am I
para nada ni va a contestar a Pero qué
telling you, I wouldn't have gotten
es lo que te digo yo no me hubiera
involved in here I understand that he is his
metido aquí a Yo entiendo que es su
friend and it hurts him or whatever gibel
amigo y le duele o lo que sea gibel te
defended you from Ricky a while ago ole ole
defendió de Ricky hace un rato ole ole
my friend gibel I was going to watch this
mi amigo gibel iba a ver este vídeo de
nauter video but I don't know if we'll have
nauter pero no sé ya si nos va a dar
time eh family but it's that we've been live for
tiempo eh familia pero es que llevamos
three and a half hours
tres horas y medi en
what the [ __ ] account did they
directo en qué [__] cuenta lo habrán
upload it on let me know if they upload it no if not we'll
subido avisarme si lo suben no si no ya
see it tomorrow if not we'll see it tomorrow this one let's see
lo vemos mañana si no ya lo vemos mañana
what the [ __ ] this one knows let's see what the
este a ver qué [__] sabrá este a ver qué
[ __ ] this one knows about strike and Ricky
[__] sabrá este de de strike y de Ricky
Eddy or anything like that Oh he has it or
Eddy ni nada por el estilo Ah lo tiene o
Lar has gotten angry with Lily Okay so
lar se ha picado con Lily Bueno hasta
far the extract of the complaint
aquí el extracto de la de la denuncia
Ricky Eddie by Lali Okay now
Ricky Eddie por parte de Lali Vale ahora
let's see what Gel said
vamos a ver qu ha dicho qu ha dicho gel
and let's also see what Gemita said
y vamos a ver también lo de lo de gemita
and I'm not going to have time for more now the
y ya no me va da tiempo a más ya lo de
Gemita thing is two extracts in fact Okay
gemita son dos extractos de hecho Bueno
while she sends me places, that's what I'm going to
mientras que me lo manda lugares eso voy
do a small extract also to
a hacer un pequeño extracto también para
tell you about Delox okay there's
comentaros lo de delox vale hay
news on the Delo issue
novedades sobre el tema de delo lo ha
Andy uploaded it let's listen to it and I'll
subido Andy revela vamos a escucharlo y
tell you because they are interesting
os comento porque son interesantes est
these little things eh nowhere and who had I
estas cositas eh ningún lado y a quien
filed a complaint against? Oh it's
sí le había puesto una denuncia Ah son
49 seconds Okay stop now we
49 segundos Bueno paraes ahora lo
put it in this extract Luares so that it
metemos en este extracto luares para que
looks more or less good to us it already went to
nos quede más o menos bien ya fue a
Delox and Delox you know that he is a client of Let's
delox y delox sabéis que es cliente de A
see  I'm going to give you a little more
ver os lo voy os voy a dar un poco más
context than what Andrea is giving,
de contexto del que está dando Andrea
okay delox. He was charged in a case in
vale delox Fue imputado en un caso en el
which he was reported for alleged fraud,
que lo denunciaron por presunta estafa
okay. Who were the ones who reported him? Well, he reported him.
vale Quiénes fueron los que lo
They agreed there, what they were doing, those who are doing now, the team, we're going to report Pambi, okay, the Christ bru, he I don't know who, he I don't know how much against the SS connection, the two of them, the two of these who are coming out now everywhere with their asses in the air
en todos lados con el culo al aire
calling a [ __ ], gabela, anyway, they are always,
llamando [__] gabela en fin siempre son
you know, we always surround ourselves with the
sabéis que siempre nos rodeamos de las
best people, okay, well, and this lawyer
mejores personas vale bueno y el abogado
who went to the gpa Channel of SS
este que fue al Canal de gpa de SS
connection, these types of channels, something very
connection este tipo de canales algo muy
curious is that these people always call
curioso es que esa gente siempre llaman
other people rape, abuse,
a otras personas violar res maltr
thieves, and those who ended up with
ladrones e y los que terminaron con
complaints and imprisoned are them. A kiss
denuncias y presos son ellos un beso
Dark, well, Ricky, for now he has a
Dark bueno Ricky de momento tiene
complaint, eh. We don't know what can
denuncia eh No sabemos lo que puede
happen, maybe he's right, eh. Hey, we do
pasar a lo mejor tiene la razón eh Oye
n't know that this lawyer who was
no lo sabemos que el abogado este que se
walking around the channels, like egun pasa
paseaba por los canales tipo egun pasa
SS conect and these types of channels, no,
SS conect y este tipo de canales no
well, Well, it turns out that this
bueno Pues resulta ser que ese
procedure  You already know that
procedimiento ya sabéis que se ha
this lawyer has been walking through YouTube channels
paseado por los canales de YouTube ese
claiming that there were a series of
abogado afirmando pues una serie de
phases, not about that complaint that Delos had
fases no sobre esa denuncia que tenía
for alleged fraud, not about the
delos por presunta estafa no del
office and such. Well, the complaint was
despacho y tal Pues bien la denuncia fue
about some christian courses that
por el tema de unos cursos cristos que
Delos gave that supposedly were a
de los dio que supuestamente era una
scam and such according to this lawyer,
estafa y tal según este abogado
eh. When you have to, before
eh Cuando tú tienes que antes de que
a year has passed under investigation, you have to
lleve un año en instrucción hay que
request that this same investigation be extended because
pedir que se prorrogue esta misma porque
the law says so and eh, the
lo lo dice la ley y eh el abogado
opposing lawyer did not request the extension
contrario no solicitó la la ampliación
when the matter was in a phase of the
cuando el tema estaba en una fase del
procedure before it is decided whether it
procedimiento antes de que se decida si
goes to trial or not, okay because it is a
se va a juicio o no vale porque es un
criminal case, it was a criminal case and I say was because there is
penal era un penal era y digo era porque
no longer one, eh. There is an extension of this
ya no hay eh Hay una prórroga de esta
investigation phase, right? Well,
fase de instrucción no Bueno pues el
this lawyer, the one who walks through all
abogado este el que se pasea por todos
the YouTube channels, forgot about the
los canales de YouTube olvidó el
procedure and missed a deadline, he
procedimiento y se le pasó un plazo él
had to go asking for it, okay, he had to,
tenía que ir pidiendo vale tenía que
this is like a leave of absence from work, he
esto es como la excedencia del trabajo
doesn't have to keep renewing it. Well,
no tiene que irla renovando Bueno pues
he forgot about the procedure and
él se le olvidó el procedimiento y se le
missed a deadline, basically the lawyer
pasó un plazo básicamente al abogado se
missed a deadline, okay. And then the case
le pasó un plazo vale Y entonces el caso
was closed. What  it happened that Pablo
quedó archivado Qué pasó que Pablo se
realized that the
dio cuenta que se le había pasado el
deadline had passed and he asked for the case to be dismissed So they are not going
plazo y pidió el archivo Así que no van
to get into whether the complaint is true or not
a entrar en si es verdad o no la
since the investigation will not continue
denuncia ya que no se va a seguir
because it cannot be exact In other
investigando porque no se puede exacto O
words, the case will no longer be judged Adelo has been
sea ya no se va a juzgar adelo ha sido
dismissed because the lawyer
archivado el caso por porque el abogado
not due to lack of evidence let's see well due to
no por falta de prueba a ver bueno por
lack of evidence I would not call it
falta de prueba yo no lo llamaría
dismissed well it has been dismissed because
archivado bueno ha sido archivado porque
the lawyer has passed the issue magically they
el abogado ha pasado el tema mágicamente
forgot well Rodrigo I have
se les olvidó bueno Rodrigo yo he
thought that but Pablo says no that it is not like that that's
pensado eso pero Pablo dice que no que
what I have thought I
no es así es que yo lo que he pensado
say here are these people now they join
digo ya está esta gente ahora se junta
with the Christ bru and now no no no no they are not
con el Cristo bru y ahora ya no no no no
fighting to denounce Delos of course
luchan por por denunciar a delos claro
now Delos He joins with them now the
ahora delos Se junta con ellos ahora el
objective is d and then the lawyer has taken
objetivo es d y entonces ha cogido el
and has passed the deadline wanting
abogado y ha pasado del plazo queriendo
that too I have thought eh But come on
eso también lo he pensado eh Pero vamos
in that case the same or rather [ __ ] has not been
en ese caso lo mismo o sea a ados no se
judged he has not been released or
le ha juzgado no ha quedado suelto ni
anything like that what happens is that the
nada por el estilo lo que pasa es que al
lawyer has missed a deadline and
abogado se le ha pasado un plazo y
then there is no case or rather the lawyer
entonces ya no hay caso o sea al abogado
of the victims It's done no  I mean
de la víctimas Ya está no O sea
eh I thought that but Pablo explained to me
eh yo he pensado eso pero me explicó
for some reason that no but no I
Pablo por alguna razón que no pero no no
can't say because I'm
puedo decir porque me lo lo estoy
looking for it and he must have told me by audio I ca
buscando y me lo habrá dicho por audio
n't find it here in the
no lo encuentro por aquí por la caja de
comments box surely if he sees it tomorrow he'll
comentarios seguro que si mañana lo ve
put it but Pablo explained it to me for some reason
lo pone pero me explicó Pablo por alguna
because I told him this morning Well that
porque yo le he dicho esta mañana Bueno
the lawyer missed
eso de que al abogado se le haya pasado
a deadline [ __ ] he must be a
un plazo [__] ya tiene que ser un
lawyer now he's not
abogado no
saying it won't be that now like Delo He gets
digo no será que ahora como el delo Se
together with the Christ bru And that troop
junta con el Cristo bru Y esa tropa
now they're no longer against Delo
ahora ya no están en contra de delo ya
now Delos is not a scammer and they
ya ya delos no es un estafador y le
must have told the lawyer that the case is
habrán dicho al abogado que el caso es
archived It's weird I mean you're going through
archive Es raro o sea estás paseándote
all the YouTube channels
por todos los canales de YouTube
saying that Delos is a scammer And
diciendo que delos es un estafador Y
now I see them capable because these
ahora yo los veo capaces porque esta
people work like that the principles they have
gente funcionan así los principios que
are those I mean suddenly Now they get
tien son esos o sea de repente Ahora son
together with Delos well no longer Now let's go now let's
se juntan con el delos pues ya no Ahora
go for we don't care about
vamos ahora vamos por ya no nos importa
your case anymore you're not a scammer now we're
tu caso ya no eres estafador ahora vamos
going after Dallas So I don't know I don't
a ir a por el Dallas Entonces no sé no
know Pablo application that he told me no
sé Pablo aplicación que me ha dicho no
no he missed the deadline for this for
no se le ha olvidado el plazo por esto
this for this so so yes
por esto por esto así que así que si
Pablo says it. It will be for some reasons
Pablo lo dice Será por algunos motivos
[Music]
[Música]